The Walt Hawver Collection
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
The Walt Hawver Collection
1939 - 1998
NPkMC-222-092
18 Linear Feet
Marist College Archives and Special Collections
Walt Hawver
This collection contains documents, letters, newspaper clippings and audio cassette tapes covering the history of Capital Cities Broadcasting for use in Walt Hawver’s published book, Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986, How the Minnow Came to Swallow the Whale. Administrative Information.
Collection Overview
The Walt Hawver Collection contains interviews, letters, audio cassettes, photographs, newspaper clippings, ratings reports, books and documents spanning from 1954 to 1998, when the transfer of materials was made to Marist College.
Acquisitions Information
Walt Hawver donated his records concerning the history of Capital Cities Broadcasting to Marist College. The project was approved by Capital Cities Executives Daniel B. Burke and Thomas S. Murphy on January 27, 1998.
Historical Note
Walter Hawver was born on February 13, 1922 in Hudson, NY. Hawver became the News Director at KTRK-TV in Houston Texas in 1969. His book, Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986, How the Minnow Came to Swallow the Whale, which chronicles Capital Cities Broadcasting’s transition from small network through its purchase of The American Broadcasting Corporation in early 1985, was published in 1994.
Restrictions to Access
There are no restrictions on this collection
Arrangement of the Collection
These records are organized into 19 series: 1) Early Albany: 1939 - 1977, 2) Minorities and Drug Policy, 3) Labor Strikes, the Fort Worth Star-Telegram and the Gathering of Small Papers, 4) Purchase of Television Properties: WKBW Buffalo, WPVI Philadelphia, KFSN Fresno, WTNH New Haven, WTDV Durham, 5) The Kansas City Star/Times, Fairchild Publicatoins and Capital Cities, Radio, 6) The Acquisition of KTRK in 1970, 7) Marvin Zindler, 8) Television History, 9) ABC and Disney, 10) Annual Reports of Capital Cities Broadcasting for the years 1957 through 1994, 11) Ratings and Consultants, 12) News Consultants, 13) KTRK Memorandums, 4) Reports, Inerview Transcripts and photographs: CCB leadership, 15) Interviews on audio cassette representing all phases of the Capital Cities experience, 16) Capital Cities/ABC: The Early Years: 1954 - 1986 Edits, 17) Capital Cities/ABC: the Early Years: 1954 - 1986 Questions, Suggestions and Correspondence, 18) Drafts and rewrites of Chapters 1 - 10 and chapter 18 of Capital Cities/ABC: The Early Years: 1954 - 1986, 19) Miscellany
- 1. Early Albany: 1939-1977, 1; 1 1 - 26
  Series contains documents, interviews, photographs and newspaper articles pertaining to the formation and operation of WTEN-TV Albany.
  By subject
  - 1939-1954: 15 Years of Television History: WRGB (Folder 1, Box 1)
  - June 25, 1956 Federal Communications Commission license to establish WTEN-TV (Folder 2, Box 1)
  - Early Albany 1965-1970: Photographs (Folder 3, Box 1)
  - Early Albany 1965-1970: Newspaper Articles (Folder 4, Box 1)
  - 1970: AFL-C10 AFTRA Contract Proposed to WTEN-WROW (two copies) (Folder 5, Box 1)
  - Documents concerning VHF and UHF, Relocation Antennas (Folder 6, Box 1)
  - Finances during WTEN establishment (Folder 7, Box 1)
  - News Analysis (Folder 8, Box 1)
  - Capital Cities Directors (Folder 9, Box 1)
  - WVET- TV versus Capital Cities (Folder 10, Box 1)
  - Management Meetings (Folder 11, Box 1)
  - Ratings (Folder 12, Box 1)
  - Interview: Masucci (Folder 13, Box 1)
  - Interview: Goldman (Folder 14, Box 1)
  - Interview: Pogan (Folder 15, Box 1)
  - Interview: Vartigan (Folder 16, Box 1)
  - Interview: Heisler (Folder 17, Box 1)
  - Interview: Collins (Folder 18, Box 1)
  - Interview: Leighton (Folder 19, Box 1)
  - Budgets for 1976 (Folder 20, Box 1)
  - Budgets for 1977 (Folder 21, Box 1)
  - Harvard Business School on Thomas Murphy and Daniel Burke (Folder 22, Box 1)
  - Special TV News Unit (Folder 23, Box 1)
  - American Bar Association Demonstration (Folder 24, Box 1)
  - WTEN memorandums (Folder 25, Box 1)
  - Capital City Pictures (Folder 26, Box 1)
- 2. Minorities and Drug Policy, 2; 1 27 - 33
  Series contains documents pertaining to minorities and drug abuse at KTRK as they relate to chapter 10 of Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986.
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 - Dealing with Minorities (Folder 27, Box 1)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 - Dealing with Minorities (Folder 28, Box 1)
  - Minorities in the Media (Folder 29, Box 1)
  - Minorities at KTRK (Folder 30, Box 1)
  - KTRK-TV Hearing October 16, 1974 (1 of 2) (Folder 31, Box 1)
  - KTRK-TV Hearing October 16, 1974 (2 of 2) (Folder 32, Box 1)
  - Regarding substance abuse in the workplace (Folder 33, Box 1)
- 3. Labor Strikes, the Fort Worth Star-Telegram and the Gathering of Small Papers, 3; 2 34 - 64
  Series contains documents and interviews pertaining to the Wilkes-Barre strike and the Fort Worth Star-Telegram as they relate to chapters 12 and 13 of Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986.
  - Wilkes-Barre Strike Chronology (1 of 3) (Folder 34, Box 2)
  - Wilkes-Barre Strike Chronology (2 of 3) (Folder 35, Box 2)
  - Wilkes-Barre Strike Chronology (3 of 3) (Folder 36, Box 2)
  - Wilkes-Barre Publishing Company Appeal (Folder 37, Box 2)
  - Wilkes-Barre Financial report (Folder 38, Box 2)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 - Wilkes-Barre (Folder 39, Box 2)
  - Interview: Conner (Folder 40, Box 2)
  - Interview: Watlack (Folder 41, Box 2)
  - Interview: Schocklee (Folder 42, Box 2)
  - Interview: Lesko et al (Folder 43, Box 2)
  - Interview: Zenick (Folder 44, Box 2)
  - Interview: Udzilla, Ted (Folder 45, Box 2)
  - Interview: Lynch (Folder 46, Box 2)
  - Interview: Bigler/Blockus (Folder 47, Box 2)
  - Interview: Golias (Folder 48, Box 2)
  - Interview: Udzilla, Jane (Folder 49, Box 2)
  - Interview: Duncan (Folder 50, Box 2)
  - Interview: Griffith (Folder 51, Box 2)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 - The Fort Worth (Folder 52, Box 2)
  - Philip J. Meek (Folder 53, Box 2)
  - Larry C. Price (Folder 54, Box 2)
  - Interview: Dick Bibb (Folder 55, Box 2)
  - Interview: Jack Butler (Folder 56, Box 2)
  - Interview: Luther Adkins (Folder 57, Box 2)
  - Interview: Jack Tinsley (Folder 58, Box 2)
  - Interview: Faires Kuykendall (Folder 59, Box 2)
  - Interview: Jerry Flemmons (Folder 60, Box 2)
  - Interview: Joseph Donth (Folder 61, Box 2)
  - Fort Worth Star-Telegram: Newspaper Articles (Folder 62, Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous Material Regarding Small Papers collected for Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 (1 of 2) (Folder 63, Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous Material Regarding Small Papers collected for Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 (2 of 2) (Folder 64, Box 2)
- 4. Purchase of Television Properties: WKBW Buffalo, WPVI Philadelphia, KFSN Fresno, WTNH New Haven, WTVD Durham, 4; 2 65 - 96
  Series contains documents and interviews about WKBW, WPVI, KFSN, WTNH and WTVD as they relate to chapter18 of Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986.
  - Original copy of Chapter 18, Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954- (Folder 65, Box 2)
  - WKBW Buffalo (Folder 66, Box 2)
  - Philip Beuth (Folder 67, Box 2)
  - Ken Johnson (Folder 68, Box 2)
  - Irv Wienstein (Folder 69, Box 2)
  - Alan Nesbitt on WKBW (Folder 70, Box 2)
  - WPVI-TV Philadelphia (Folder 71, Box 2)
  - Walter Anneberg (Folder 72, Box 2)
  - Alan Nesbitt on WPVI-TV (Folder 73, Box 2)
  - Art Moore (Folder 74, Box 2)
  - Charlie Bradley (Folder 75, Box 2)
  - Jon Miller (Folder 76, Box 2)
  - Larry Pollock (Folder 77, Box 2)
  - Gene McCurdy (Folder 78, Box 2)
  - The death of Jim O’Brien (Folder 79, Box 2)
  - KFSN Fresno (Folder 80, Box 2)
  - WTNH New Haven (Folder 81, Box 2)
  - Peter Orne (Folder 82, Box 2)
  - Lil Sullivan/D. Carmen Iannucci (Folder 83, Box 2)
  - CCB Offering Circular (Folder 84, Box 2)
  - Floyd Fletcher, first interview (Folder 85, Box 2)
  - WTVD Durham (Folder 86, Box 2)
  - Paul Bures (Folder 87, Box 2)
  - Erwin Hester (Folder 88, Box 2)
  - Richard Appleton (Folder 89, Box 2)
  - Miriam Bly (Folder 90, Box 2)
  - Peggy Mann (Folder 91, Box 2)
  - Marie Brian (Folder 92, Box 2)
  - Ernie Greup and Ed Wall (Folder 93, Box 2)
  - Ed Wall on the fire at WTVD (Folder 94, Box 2)
  - Floyd Fletcher, second interview (Folder 95, Box 2)
  - Miscellaneous (Folder 96, Box 2)
- 5. The Kansas City Star/Times, Fairchild Publications and Capital Cities Radio, 5; 3 97 - 127
  Series contains documents and interviews about The Kansas City Star/Times, Fairchild Publications and Capital Cities Radio as they relate to chapters 8 and 12 of Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986.
  - Kansas City Star Centennial Publication (see flat box 12A) (Folder 97, Box 3)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Chapter 12: The Kansas City Star/Times early versions and edits (Folder 98, Box 3)
  - The Capital Cities Purchase of The Kansas City Star/Times (Folder 99, Box 3)
  - Labor (Folder 100, Box 3)
  - Ben Schifman (Folder 101, Box 3)
  - Joe McGuff (Folder 102, Box 3)
  - Jim Fisher (Folder 103, Box 3)
  - George Burg (Folder 104, Box 3)
  - Jim Hale (Folder 105, Box 3)
  - Cruise Palmer/W.W. Baker (Folder 106, Box 3)
  - Newspaper: A Century of Election History (Folder 107, Box 3)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Chapter 8: Fairchild Publications, Inc. early versions and edits (Folder 108, Box 3)
  - Fairchild Publications (Folder 109, Box 3)
  - Philip McGovern (Folder 110, Box 3)
  - Marty Rosenblum (Folder 111, Box 3)
  - John Fairchild (Folder 112, Box 3)
  - Michael Coady (Folder 113, Box 3)
  - Radio 1960-1990 (Folder 114, Box 3)
  - Radio: Master File (Folder 115, Box 3)
  - Bob Peebles: WROW (Folder 116, Box 3)
  - James Arcara (Folder 117, Box 3)
  - Joe Somerset (Folder 118, Box 3)
  - WPAT AM/FM (Folder 119, Box 3)
  - Aaron Daniels (Folder 120, Box 3)
  - Norm Schrutt: WBIE (Folder 121, Box 3)
  - WJR (Folder 122, Box 3)
  - James Quello (Folder 123, Box 3)
  - Warren Potash: WBAP (Folder 124, Box 3)
  - WKBW Radio (Folder 125, Box 3)
  - WPRO Radio (Folder 126, Box 3)
  - L.A. Radio (Folder 127, Box 3)
- 6. The Acquisition of KTRK in 1970, 6; 3 128 - 146
  Series contains documents, interviews and memos pertaining to the Capital Cities Purchase of KTRK.
  - Police versus KTRK (Folder 128, Box 3)
  - Jim Priest (Folder 129, Box 3)
  - Violence on television (Folder 130, Box 3)
  - News Anchors (Folder 131, Box 3)
  - KTRK Miscellaneous (Folder 132, Box 3)
  - Boys for Sale (Folder 133, Box 3)
  - Bill Walbridge (Folder 134, Box 3)
  - Pluria Marshall (Folder 135, Box 3)
  - David Ward (Folder 136, Box 3)
  - Jim Masucci (Folder 137, Box 3)
  - Ken Johnson (Folder 138, Box 3)
  - Allen Pengelly (Folder 139, Box 3)
  - Pete Hoffman (Folder 140, Box 3)
  - Peggy Mann (Folder 141, Box 3)
  - KTRK-TV news Stylebook (Folder 142, Box 3)
  - Memos to the news director (Folder 143, Box 3)
  - Walt Hawver/KTRK: first year (Folder 144, Box 3)
  - Early KTRK Early WPVI Anchor News (Folder 145, Box 3)
  - KTRK ratings (Folder 146, Box 3)
- 7. Marvin Zindler, 7; 3 147 - 163
  Series contains documents, publications, interviews, letters and newspaper articles about Capital Cities Employee Marvin Zindler.
  Arrangemnet: By subject
  - The many Faces of Marvin Zindler by Kent Demaret (Folder 147, Box 3)
  - “The Best Little Whorehouse in Texas” (Folder 148, Box 3)
  - Whorehouse Story (Folder 149, Box 3)
  - Colonel Wilson Spears and Attorney General John Hill (Folder 150, Box 3)
  - Sheriff T.J. Flourney (Folder 151, Box 3)
  - District Attorney Oliver Kitzman: Fayette, Austin Counties (Folder 152, Box 3)
  - Original Scripts: 1973 (Folder 153, Box 3)
  - The Sheriff Attacks (Folder 154, Box 3)
  - Whorehouse Satire (Folder 155, Box 3)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 Chapter 18 original (Folder 156, Box 3)
  - Zindler letters (Folder 157, Box 3)
  - Dr. Levy re: libel (Folder 158, Box 3)
  - “Ranch” letters (Folder 159, Box 3)
  - Zindler’s Suspension (Folder 160, Box 3)
  - Nazi Party Threat (Folder 161, Box 3)
  - Miscellaneous (Folder 162, Box 3)
- 8. Television History, 8; 4 163 - 193
  Series contains documents, press releases, photographs, letters, newspaper articles and scripts relating to the history of television between 1950 and 1985.
  - 1950s Networks (Folder 163, Box 4)
  - Network Television Show Press Releases and Promotional Photographs (Folder 164, Box 4)
  - Walt Hawver newspaper articles 1950s: Quiz Show Scandal, Payola, and Jack Parr Walk-off (1 of 2) (Folder 165, Box 4)
  - Walt Hawver newspaper articles 1950s: Quiz Show Scandal, Payola, and Jack Parr Walk-off (2 of 2) (Folder 166, Box 4)
  - Walt Hawver newspaper articles 1956-1957: Television and radio reviews, Albany Knickerbocker News and other papers (1 of 2) (Folder 167, Box 4)
  - Walt Hawver newspaper articles 1956-1957: Television and radio reviews, Albany Knickerbocker News and other papers (2 of 2) (Folder 168, Box 4)
  - Television 1957- 1962: “It’s a Man’s World,” Ratings, Pay TV and Comedians. (Folder 169, Box 4)
  - Walt Hawver newspaper articles: experimental theatre coverage (Folder 170, Box 4)
  - Letters to Walt Hawver 1955-1963: In reaction to radio-TV reviews in Albany Knickerbocker News (1 of 2) (Folder 171, Box 4)
  - Letters to Walt Hawver 1955-1963: In reaction to radio-TV reviews in Albany Knickerbocker News (2 of 2) (Folder 172, Box 4)
  - Partial Expense Reports 1985- 1993 (Folder 173, Box 4)
  - Correspondence 1985 (Folder 174, Box 4)
  - CCB Phones (Folder 175, Box 4)
  - CCB Officers 1959- 1985 (Folder 176, Box 4)
  - CCB Chronology (Folder 177, Box 4)
  - Murphy Years Chronology (Folder 178, Box 4)
  - General Manager/ News Director Summaries (Folder 179, Box 4)
  - Publishing Summary (Folder 180, Box 4)
  - Public Service Summary (Folder 181, Box 4)
  - Radio Summary (Folder 182, Box 4)
  - NBC TV Opera script: War and Peace (Folder 183, Box 4)
  - “The Kaiser Aluminum Hour” script: Antigone (Folder 184, Box 4)
  - Hallmark Hall of Fame script: The Christmas Tree (Folder 185, Box 4)
  - NBC TV Opera script: Rigoletto (Folder 186, Box 4)
  - Hallmark Hall of Fame script: Berkeley Square (Folder 187, Box 4)
  - NBC TV script: The Living End (Folder 188, Box 4)
  - CBS transcript: Arthur Godfrey-Jackie Gleason Talk-Fest (Folder 189, Box 4)
  - NBC TV script: Way of the Cross (Folder 190, Box 4)
  - script: The Real West (Folder 191, Box 4)
  - NBC TV script: The General Motors Fiftieth Anniversary Show (Folder 192, Box 4)
  - script: Lee at Gettysburg (Folder 193, Box 4)
- 9. ABC and Disney, 9; 5 194 - 201
  Alphabetical
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 - Chapter 20 early draft (Folder 194, Box 5)
  - Capital Cities/ABC, the Early Years: 1954-1986 - Prelude early draft 196- Capital Cities/ABC merger announcement 3/18/85 (Folder 195, Box 5)
  - Newspaper articles: Capital Cities purchase of ABC (1 of 3) (Folder 197, Box 5)
  - Newspaper articles: Capital Cities purchase of ABC (2 of 3) (Folder 198, Box 5)
  - Newspaper articles: Capital Cities purchase of ABC (3 of 3) (Folder 199, Box 5)
  - Disney/ABC merger (1 of 2) (Folder 200, Box 5)
  - Disney/ABC merger (2 of 2) (Folder 201, Box 5)
- 10. Annual reports of Capital Cities Broadcasting for the years 1957 through 1994, 1955 - 1995; 10; 5 202 - 279
  Series contains annual reports for Capital Cities from 1957 through 1994 for stockholders and executives.
  Chronological
  - CCB Annual Report preview: 1955 (Folder 202, Box 5)
  - CCB Annual Report preview: 1956 (Folder 203, Box 5)
  - CCB Annual Report: 1957 (Folder 204, Box 5)
  - CCB Annual Report: 1958 (Folder 205, Box 5)
  - CCB Annual Report: 1959 (Folder 206, Box 5)
  - CCB Annual Report: 1960 (Folder 207, Box 5)
  - CCB Annual Report: 1961 (Folder 208, Box 5)
  - CCB Annual Report: 1962 (Folder 209, Box 5)
  - CCB Annual Report: 1963 (Folder 210, Box 5)
  - CCB Annual Report: 1964 (Folder 211, Box 5)
  - CCB Annual Report: 1965 (Folder 212, Box 5)
  - CCB Annual Report: 1966 (Folder 213, Box 5)
  - CCB Annual Report: 1967 (Folder 214, Box 5)
  - CCB Annual Report: 1968 (Folder 215, Box 5)
  - CCB Annual Report: 1969 (Folder 216, Box 5)
  - CCB Annual Report: 1970 (Folder 217, Box 5)
  - CCB Annual Report: 1971 (Folder 218, Box 5)
  - CCB Annual Report: 1972 (Folder 219, Box 5)
  - CCB Annual Report: 1973 (Folder 220, Box 5)
  - CCB Annual Report: 1974 (Folder 221, Box 5)
  - CCB Annual Report: 1975 (Folder 222, Box 5)
  - CCB Annual Report: 1976 (Folder 223, Box 5)
  - CCB Annual Report: 1977 (Folder 224, Box 5)
  - CCB Annual Report: 1978 (Folder 225, Box 5)
  - CCB Annual Report: 1979 (Folder 226, Box 5)
  - CCB Annual Report: 1980 (Folder 227, Box 5)
  - CCB Annual Report: 1981 (Folder 228, Box 5)
  - CCB Annual Report: 1982 (Folder 229, Box 5)
  - CCB Annual Report: 1983 (Folder 230, Box 5)
  - CCB Annual Report: 1984 (Folder 231, Box 5)
  - CCB Annual Report: 1985 (Folder 232, Box 5)
  - CCB Annual Report: 1986 (Folder 233, Box 5)
  - CCB Annual Report: 1987 (Folder 234, Box 5)
  - CCB Annual Report: 1988 (Folder 235, Box 5)
  - CCB Annual Report: 1989 (Folder 236, Box 5)
  - CCB Annual Report: 1990 (Folder 237, Box 5)
  - CCB Annual Report: 1991 (Folder 238, Box 5)
  - CCB Annual Report: 1992 (Folder 239, Box 5)
  - CCB Annual Report: 1993 (Folder 240, Box 5)
  - CCB Annual Report: 1994 (2 copies) (Folder 241, Box 5)
  - ABC Annual Report: 1984 (Folder 242, Box 5)
  - CCB Stockholder’s Call 1985 (Folder 243, Box 5)
  - CCB/ABC Stockholder’s Call 1995 (Folder 244, Box 5)
- 11. Ratings and Consultants, 11; 6 245 - 273
  Series contains documents, and audio cassette tapes pertaining to analysis of ratings for KTRK in the Houston Market between 1967 and 1985.
  - KTRK analysis and Houston Television Market: 1967 to 1985 (Folder 245, Box 6)
  - Houston Rating Trends (Folder 246, Box 6)
  - Ratings Information: 1974 (Folder 247, Box 6)
  - Ratings Information: 1975 (Folder 248, Box 6)
  - Ratings Information: 1976 (Folder 249, Box 6)
  - Ratings Information: 1977 (Folder 250, Box 6)
  - Ratings Information: 1978 (Folder 251, Box 6)
  - Ratings Information: 1979 (Folder 252, Box 6)
  - Ratings Information: 1980 (Folder 253, Box 6)
  - Ratings Information: 1981 (Folder 254, Box 6)
  - Ratings Information: 1982 (Folder 255, Box 6)
  - Ratings Information: 1983 (Folder 256, Box 6)
  - Ratings Information: 1984 (Folder 257, Box 6)
  - Ratings Information: 1985 (Folder 258, Box 6)
  - Houston Television Viewers 1973-1985 (Folder 259, Box 6)
  - Houston Chronicle Post newspaper articles on ratings (Folder 260, Box 6)
  - McHugh/Hoffman: KTRK Consultants (1 of 2) (Folder 261, Box 6)
  - McHugh/Hoffman: KTRK Consultants (2 of 2) (Folder 262, Box 6)
  - Other KTRK Consultants (Folder 263, Box 6)
  - Society of Professional Journalists National Convention, October 19-22, 1989 audio cassette tape 3 (Folder Item 264, Box 6)
  - Society of Professional Journalists National Convention, October 19-22, 1989 audio cassette tape 4 (Folder Item 265, Box 6)
  - Society of Professional Journalists National Convention, October 19-22, 1989 audio cassette tape 6 (Folder Item 266, Box 6)
  - Society of Professional Journalists National Convention, October 19-22, 1989 audio cassette tape 13 (Folder Item 267, Box 6)
  - Society of Professional Journalists National Convention, October 19-22, 1989 audio cassette tape 14 (Folder Item 268, Box 6)
  - Society of Professional Journalists National Convention, October 19-22, 1989 audio cassette tape 17 (Folder Item 269, Box 6)
  - Society of Professional Journalists National Convention, October 19-22 (Folder Item 270, Box 6)
  - Society of Professional Journalists National Convention, October 19-22, 1989 audio cassette tape 29 (Folder Item 271, Box 6)
  - Society of Professional Journalists National Convention, October 19-22, 1989 audio cassette tape 38 (Folder Item 272, Box 6)
  - Society of Professional Journalists National Convention, October 19-22, 1989 audio cassette tape 3 (Folder Item 273, Box 6)
- 12. News Consultants, 12; Boxes: 7 - 8 274 - 349
  Series contains documents, surveys, polls and market reports conducted by KTRK, Nielson, ARB, Arbitron and McHugh and Hoffman Inc. to assess audience viewership in the Houston area between 1960 and 1983.
  Chronological by subject
  - KTRK-TV Executive Summary Statewide Opinion Survey January, 1977 (Folder 274, Box 7)
  - KTRK-TV Statewide Media Survey April, 1977 (2 copies) (Folder 275, Box 7)
  - KTRK-TV Texas Statewide Media Poll July, 1977 (Folder 276, Box 7)
  - KTRK-TV Statewide Opinion Survey October, 1977 (Folder 277, Box 7)
  - KTRK-TV Texas Media Survey January, 1978 (2 copies) (Folder 278, Box 7)
  - KTRK-TV Houston, Texas Statewide Political Opinion Survey April 1978 (Folder 279, Box 7)
  - KTRK-TV Statewide Media Survey July, 1978 (3 copies) (Folder 280, Box 7)
  - KTRK-TV Statewide Media Survey October 30-31, 1978 (2 copies) (Folder 281, Box 7)
  - KTRK-TV Education Survey January- February, 1979 (Folder 282, Box 7)
  - KTRK-TV Opinion Poll (July 24-27, 1979) (2 copies) (Folder 283, Box 7)
  - KTRK-TV Survey October 28-29, 1979 Houston Mayoral Election (2 (Folder 284, Box 7)
  - KTRK-TV Special Survey: Perceptions of Blacks/Black Progress in (Folder 285, Box 7)
  - Computer Printout for Texas Media Poll (Folder 286, Box 7)
  - Nielson Station Index: Albany-Schenectady-Troy Area: Dec. 6, 1960 (Folder 287, Box 7)
  - Nielson Station Index: Albany-Schenectady-Troy Area: Oct. 30- Nov. (Folder 288, Box 7)
  - Nielson Station Index: Albany-Schenectady-Troy Area: Mar. 11- Apr. 7, 1963 (Folder 289, Box 7)
  - Nielson Station Index: Albany-Schenectady-Troy Area: Oct. 28- Nov. 24, 1963 (Folder 290, Box 7)
  - Nielson Station Index: Albany-Schenectady-Troy Area: Nov. 5- Dec. 2, 1964 (Folder 291, Box 7)
  - Nielson Station Index: Albany-Schenectady-Troy Area: Nov. 1965 293- Nielson Station Index: Albany-Schenectady-Troy Area: Feb. 1966 (Folder 292, Box 7)
  - Nielson Station Index: Albany-Schenectady-Troy Area: June 1966 (Folder 294, Box 7)
  - Nielson Station Index: Albany-Schenectady-Troy Area: Oct. - Nov. (Folder 295, Box 7)
  - Nielson Station Index: Albany-Schenectady-Troy Area: Feb.- Mar. (Folder 296, Box 7)
  - Nielson Station Index: Albany-Schenectady-Troy Area: June 1967 (Folder 297, Box 7)
  - Nielson Station Index: Albany-Schenectady-Troy Area: Nov. 1967 (Folder 298, Box 7)
  - Nielson Station Index: Albany-Schenectady-Troy Area: Feb.- Mar. (Folder 299, Box 7)
  - Nielson Station Index: Albany-Schenectady-Troy Area: May 1968 (Folder 300, Box 7)
  - Nielson Station Index: Albany-Schenectady-Troy Area: May 1968 (Folder 301, Box 7)
  - Nielson Station Index: Albany-Schenectady-Troy Area: Feb.- Mar. (Folder 302, Box 7)
  - Nielson Station Index: Albany-Schenectady-Troy Area: May 1969 (Folder 303, Box 7)
  - Nielson Station Index: Albany-Schenectady-Troy Area: Nov. 1969 (Folder 304, Box 7)
  - Nielson Station Index: Albany-Schenectady-Troy Area: Feb.- Mar. (Folder 305, Box 7)
  - Nielson Station Index: Albany-Schenectady-Troy Area: May 1970 (Folder 306, Box 7)
  - Nielson Station Index: Albany-Schenectady-Troy Area: May 1971 (Folder 307, Box 7)
  - Nielson Station Index: Albany-Schenectady-Troy Area: May 1981 (Folder 308, Box 7)
  - ARB Market Report Albany-Schenectady-Troy TV audience: Mar. 1961 (Folder 309, Box 7)
  - ARB Market Report Albany-Schenectady-Troy TV audience: Mar. 1962 (Folder 310, Box 7)
  - ARB Market Report Albany-Schenectady-Troy TV audience: Mar. 1964 (Folder 311, Box 7)
  - ARB Market Report Albany-Schenectady-Troy TV audience: Nov. 1965 (Folder 312, Box 7)
  - ARB Market Report Albany-Schenectady-Troy TV audience: Mar. 1966 (Folder 313, Box 7)